YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 8. Community Associations
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. COMMUNITY ASSOCIATIONS FILES
  - Subseries B. 1988-2002
    - Illinois
      - McLean County (Bloomington)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-99 (Box 909)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 909)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 909)
        - Board of Directors, 1997-99 (Box 909)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 909)
        - Correspondence, 1992-98, n.d. (Box 909)
        - Program, 1989, n.d. (Box 909)
      - Pekin
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 909)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 909)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 909)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 909)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-97 (Box 909)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1928, 1995 (Box 909)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box 909)
      - Peoria
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 910)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-96 (Box 910)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 910)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 910)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1925, 1996 (Box 910)
        - Correspondence, 1986-98 (Box 910)
      - Quad Cities (Rock Island) [serves Rock Island and Moline, IL, and Davenport and Bettendorf, IA]
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 910)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 910)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 910)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 910)
        - Board of Directors, 1993, 1997 (Box 910)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1891, 1973-77, 1993, 1998 (Box 910)
        - Correspondence, 1977-99 (Box 910)
        - Program, 1991-94, n.d. (Box 910)
      - Quincy
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 910)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 910)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 910)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 910)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-95 (Box 910)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1905, 1994, 1996 (Box 910)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2000, n.d. (Box 910)
        - Program, 1981-2000 (Box 910)
      - Rockford
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 910)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 910)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 910)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 910)
        - Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 910)
        - Correspondence, 1986-99 (Box 910)
        - Program, 1992-98, n.d. (Box 910)
      - St. Clair County (Belleville)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 910)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 910)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 910)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 910)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1996 (Box 910)
        - Correspondence, 1985-99 (Box 910)
      - Sauk Valley/Sterling-Rock Falls (Sterling)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 910)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 910)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 910)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 910)
        - Board of Directors, 1993-99, n.d. (Box 910)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1990-95 (Box 910)
        - Correspondence, 1984-99 (Box 910)
        - Program, 1993, 1997-98 (Box 910)
      - Springfield
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-99 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1909-96 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1978-2000 (Box 911)
    - Indiana
      - Anderson
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-98 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 911)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 911)
        - Board of Directors, 1992-93 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1920-96 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1986-98, n.d. (Box 911)
        - Program, 1976-97 (Box 911)
      - Calumet Area (Hammond)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-92 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1980-99 (Box 911)
        - Program, 1992-93, n.d. (Box 911)
      - Elkhart County (Elkhart)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 911)
        - Board of Directors, 1980-81, 1996-97 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1997 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2000 (Box 911)
        - Program, 1981, 1997 (Box 911)
      - Evansville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 911)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 911)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-92 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1989-98, n.d. (Box 911)
      - Fort Wayne
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 911)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-92 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1991-2001 (Box 911)
        - Program, 1987-2002 (Box 911)
      - Gary
        - Accreditation requirements, 1988-98 (Box 911)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-98 (Box 911)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997 (Box 911)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 911)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993-97 (Box 911)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 912)
      - Indianapolis
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 912)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 912)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997-98 (Box 912)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 912)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 912)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1989-98 (Box 912)
        - Correspondence, 1985-2001, n.d. (Box 912)
        - Program, 1988-98, n.d. (Box 912)
      - Kokomo
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 912)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-96 (Box 912)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 912)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 912)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98 (Box 912)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994-96, n.d. (Box 912)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2002, n.d. (Box 912)
        - Program, 1989-96, n.d. (Box 912)
      - Lafayette, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1992-99 (Box 912)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 912)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 912)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 912)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1932, 1984-95, n.d. (Box 912)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 912)
        - Program, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 912)
      - Marion
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 912)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 912)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995 (Box 912)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 912)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996-98 (Box 912)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 912)
      - Muncie
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 912)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 912)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 912)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 912)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98 (Box 912)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1911, 1990-98 (Box 912)
        - Correspondence, 1990-98 (Box 912)
        - Legal
          - Correspondence, 1994-97 (Box 913)
          - Pitts v. YWCA of Muncie, May- Jul 1996 (Box 913)
          - State of Indiana Civil Rights Commission v. YWCA
            - Summonses, Jul 1996 (Box 913)
            - Motions to dismiss and memoranda in support thereof, 15 Oct 1996 (Box 913)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 913)
      - Richmond
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 913)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-99 (Box 913)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 913)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 913)
        - Board of Directors, 1997-98, n.d. (Box 913)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1959-2001 (Box 913)
        - Correspondence, 1987-98 (Box 913)
        - Program, 1993-98, n.d. (Box 913)
      - Saint Joseph County (South Bend)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 913)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 913)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1996 (Box 913)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 913)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1997 (Box 913)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box 913)
      - Terre Haute
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 913)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 913)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 913)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 913)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1997 (Box 913)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 913)
        - Program, 1981, 1996 (Box 913)
    - Iowa
      - Atlantic (Registered Adult Advisory Group), 1988-99 (Box 913)
      - Black Hawk County (Waterloo)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 913)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 913)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 913)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 913)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 2000 (Box 913)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2000 (Box 913)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 913)
      - Burlington
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 913)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-98 (Box 913)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 913)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 913)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1992-98 (Box 913)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2000, n.d. (Box 913)
        - Program, 1989-98, n.d. (Box 913)
      - Cedar Rapids and Linn County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 914)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-98 (Box 914)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 914)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 914)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-2000 (Box 914)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995-96 (Box 914)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 914)
        - Program, 1992-96, n.d. (Box 914)
      - Clarinda Y-Women (Registered Adult Advisory Group), 1979, 1994-2003 (Box 914)
      - Clinton County/Gateway (Clinton)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 914)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 914)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 914)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 914)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993-97 (Box 914)
        - Correspondence, 1993-2000 (Box 914)
        - Program, 1980-2000, n.d. (Box 914)
      - Creston Community (Registered Adult Group), 1992 (Box 914)
      - Des Moines, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 914)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 914)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-95 (Box 914)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 914)
        - Board of Directors, 1993-98 (Box 914)
        - Branch, Greater Altoona Community Service Campus: potential provisional status, 1993-96 (Box 914)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1997-98 (Box 914)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2000, n.d. (Box 914)
        - Program, 1994-2000 (Box 914)
      - Dubuque
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 914)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 914)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 914)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 914)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1996 (Box 914)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 914)
      - Fort Dodge
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 914)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 914)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 914)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 914)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-2000, n.d. (Box 914)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1959-2000 (Box 914)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2000, n.d. (Box 914)
        - Program, 1998-99, n.d. (Box 914)
      - Marshalltown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 915)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 915)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 915)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 915)
        - Board of Directors, 1993-98 (Box 915)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993-98 (Box 915)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 915)
        - Program, 1998-2000 (Box 915)
      - Muscatine
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-96 (Box 915)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-96 (Box 915)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1992-95 (Box 915)
        - Board of Directors, 1989-95 (Box 915)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1952-95 (Box 915)
        - Correspondence, 1981-97, n.d. (Box 915)
        - Program, 1989-95, n.d. (Box 915)
      - Oskaloosa
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 915)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-97 (Box 915)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 915)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1998 (Box 915)
        - Correspondence, 1992-99, n.d. (Box 915)
      - Ottumwa
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-97 (Box 915)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-96 (Box 915)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 915)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996-98 (Box 915)
        - Correspondence, 1992-99 (Box 915)
      - Washington
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 915)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 915)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 915)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 915)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-99 (Box 915)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1978-96 (Box 915)
        - Correspondence, 1985-2001 (Box 915)
        - Program, 1986-96, n.d. (Box 915)
    - Kansas
      - General, 1984-87 (Box 915)
      - Registered Groups, 1987-91 (Box 915)
      - Cunningham (Adult Advisory Group), 1993-95 (Box 915)
      - Holton, 1989 (Box 915)
      - Independence, 1981-89 (Box 915)
      - Jewell (Adult Advisory Group), 1993-95 (Box 915)
      - Kansas City
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 915)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 915)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 915)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 915)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-95 (Box 915)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1989-96 (Box 915)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2001 (Box 915)
        - Legal, 1989 (Box 915)
        - Program, 1993-2001, n.d. (Box 915)
      - Leavenworth
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1975-78, 1989 (Box 916)
        - Correspondence, 1975-96, n.d. (Box 916)
        - Personnel confidential, 1983-90 (Box 916)
        - Program, 1986-93 (Box 916)
      - Salina
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 916)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 916)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 916)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 916)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1998 (Box 916)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 916)
        - Program, 1990-99 (Box 916)
      - Stafford, 1995 (Box 916)
      - Topeka
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 916)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 916)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 916)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 916)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1986, 1996, n.d. (Box 916)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box 916)
        - Program, 1992-2000 (Box 916)
      - Valley Falls (Adult Advisory Group), 1989-2001 (Box 916)
      - Wichita
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 916)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 916)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 916)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 916)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-96, n.d. (Box 916)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994-99 (Box 916)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 916)
        - Program, 1994-98, n.d. (Box 916)
    - Kentucky
      - Ashland
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 916)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 916)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 916)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 916)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1978, 1994 (Box 916)
        - Correspondence, 1985-2002, n.d. (Box 916)
      - Lexington
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 916)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 916)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, n.d. (Box 916)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 916)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-97 (Box 916)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1950-95 (Box 916)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 916)
        - Program, 1992-2000, n.d. (Box 916)
      - Louisville and Jefferson County, 1987 (Box 917)
    - Louisiana
      - Alexandria-Pineville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 917)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 917)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998. (Box 917)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1974, 1996 (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1988-98, n.d. (Box 917)
      - Baton Rouge
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 917)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-99 (Box 917)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 917)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1947-96 (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1950-68, 1992-98 (Box 917)
        - Historical, 1967 (Box 917)
        - Program, 1983-97 (Box 917)
      - Bayou Area/Bayou Parishes (Houma)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-91 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1985 (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1984-93 (Box 917)
        - Program, 1985-91, n.d. (Box 917)
      - Bogalusa
        - Accreditation requirements, 1992-99 (Box 917)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-99 (Box 917)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 917)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1975, 1995, n.d. (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1992-97, n.d. (Box 917)
      - New Orleans
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 917)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-2000 (Box 917)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-98 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1997, 1999 (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2002, n.d. (Box 917)
        - Program, 1995-96 (Box 917)
      - Northeast Louisiana/Monroe
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 917)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 917)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 917)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1979-99 (Box 917)
      - Northwest Louisiana (Shreveport)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 917)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-97 (Box 917)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 917)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 917)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1953, 1994-97 (Box 917)
        - Correspondence, 1978-99, n.d. (Box 917)
        - Program, 1996-97, n.d. (Box 917)
    - Maine
      - Bangor-Brewer
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 918)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 918)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 918)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 918)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1979, 1995 (Box 918)
        - Correspondence, 1978-2000, n.d. (Box 918)
        - Program, 1970-2001, n.d. (Box 918)
      - Central Maine/Lewiston-Auburn (Lewiston)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 918)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1996-97 (Box 918)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 918)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 918)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1931, 1979, 1998 (Box 918)
        - Correspondence, 1981-2000 (Box 918)
        - Program, 1979-91 (Box 918)
      - Mount Desert Island (Bar Harbor)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 918)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 918)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 918)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 918)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993, 1998 (Box 918)
        - Correspondence, 1983-2000 (Box 918)
        - Program, 1995, 1997, n.d. (Box 918)
      - Portland, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 918)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-97 (Box 918)
        - Action Audit, 1977-80 (Box 918)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 918)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 918)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996, 1998 (Box 918)
        - Correspondence, 1983-2001 (Box 918)
        - Program, 1995, 1998, n.d. (Box 918)
      - York County (Saco)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-95 (Box 918)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1967-85 (Box 918)
        - Correspondence, 1991-99 (Box 918)
        - Program, 1982-85 (Box 918)
    - Maryland
      - Annapolis and Anne Arundel County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 918)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 918)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 918)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 918)
        - Board of Directors, 1985-96, n.d. (Box 918)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1966, 1994-95 (Box 918)
        - Correspondence, 1984-2000, n.d. (Box 918)
        - Program, 1993-97, n.d. (Box 918)
      - Baltimore, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 919)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 919)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995-98 (Box 919)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 919)